Inventory of the Richard Throssel Papers, 1900-1993 (bulk 1902-1933)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Photographs and Negatives, 1902-ca. 1920s; Series I.; 14.86 cubic ft. (6 letter boxes, 1 F24 box, 39 negative boxes, 5 shoe boxes and 4 F20 boxes).
  - 4 x 5 Glass Plate Negatives and Photographs, Subseries II.
    - Men on Horseback - Back View (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1019
    - Men on Horseback - Back View (Box 5, Folder 4)
      TP1020
    - Men Riding Horses Over Hill (Box 5, Folder 5)
      TP1021
    - Men Driving Herd of Horses (Box 5, Folder 5)
      TP1022
    - Men Preparing Horses for Riding (Box 5, Folder 5)
      TP1023
    - Man Preparing Food in Cave (Box 5, Folder 5)
      TP1024
    - Wagon with Belongings and a Horse in Grove of Trees (Box 5, Folder 5)
      TP1025
    - Man Riding Over Rocky Terrain with Packhorse (Box 5, Folder 6)
      TP1026
    - Two Men Riding Near Grove of Aspens (Box 5, Folder 6)
      TP1027
      1 celluloid negative 3½ x 6
    - Man Riding Horse Over Road (Box 5, Folder 6)
      TP1028
    - Man Following Three Horses in Snow (Box 5, Folder 6)
      TP1029
    - Watering Horses (Box 5, Folder 6)
      TP1030
    - Men Riding Next to River (Box 5, Folder 6)
      TP1031
    - Two Men in Western Attire - House in Background (Box 5, Folder 6)
      TP1032
    - Cowboy Holding Horse by the Leg (Box 5, Folder 6)
      TP1033
  - Celluloid/Glass Negatives and Photographs, Subseries III.
    - Cowboy Riding Horse While Holding U.S. Flag (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1034
    - Cowhands with Two Women (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1035
    - Photographer with Two Cameras in Mountain Setting (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1036
    - Photographer with Horseback Rider (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1037
    - Man on Horseback with Pack Horse (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1038
    - Two Men with Horses at Ruins of Adobe Wall (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1039
    - Man Watching Herd of Cattle (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1040
    - Man Watching Herd of Cattle (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1041
    - Man Watching Herd of Cattle (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1042
    - Men with Horses - Wagon in Background (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1043
    - Men Riding Horseback (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1044
    - Man on Horseback Leading Packhorse (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1045
    - Men Riding Horseback on Rocky Terrain - Back View (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1046
    - Man on Horseback Leading Two Packhorses Loaded with Camera Equipment (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1047
      1 celluloid negative 3 x 4
    - Two Men on Horseback, Packhorses, and Spectators (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1048
      1 celluloid negative 2½ x 4
    - Camp Scene - Tent, Two Wheel Wagon, Man Resting in Grass (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1049
    - "Sunrise at Custer" - Cowhands Eating at Campsite (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1050
    - Horses in River (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1051
    - Horses in Field (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1052
    - Horses Walking into River (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1053
    - Horses Laying Down in Field (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1054
    - Horse Herd (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1055
    - Horses in Grove of Trees (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1056
    - White Dog (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1057
    - Dog Laying Down (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1058
      1 celluloid negative 3 x 6
    - Dog (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1059
      1 celluloid negative 2 x 4½
    - Dog Laying on Couch (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1060
      2 celluloid negatives 3 x 6
    - "Camp Greetings" - Dog (Box 5, Folder 7)
      TP1061
    - Bear in Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1062
    - Bear in Dumping Ground (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1063
    - Caged Bear (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1064
    - Man Playing with Bear (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1065
    - Bear on Log (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1066
    - Swan (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1067
    - Chicken (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1068
    - Chicken with Chicks (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1069
    - Chicks (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1070
    - Two Geese (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1071
    - Eagle in Grass (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1072
    - Bird in Grass (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1073
    - Skunk (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1074
    - "Montana Game Birds" - Skunk (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1075
    - Monkey Chained Near Pen (Box 5, Folder 8)
      TP1076
    - Two Deer in Brush (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1077
    - Two Deer in Snow (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1078
    - Two Buck Deer with Doe in Snow (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1079
    - Two Doe Deer in Snow (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1080
    - Two Bucks with Velvet on Antlers (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1081
    - Dead Buck Deer with Rifle on Top (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1082
      2 lantern slides 3 x 4
    - Bull Elk Closeup (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1083
    - Bull Elk Side Profile (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1084
    - Two Bull Elk (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1085
    - Bull Elk with Cow Elk (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1086
    - Elk - Back View (Box 5, Folder 9)
      TP1087
    - Bull Elk Closeup (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1088
    - Bull Elk Side Profile (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1089
    - Bull Elk Side Profile (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1090
    - Bull Elk with Cow Elk (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1091
    - Bull Elk with Cow Elk Laying Down (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1092
    - Two Elk Running Away (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1093
    - Bull Elk with Two Cow Elk (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1094
    - "Elk by Fairgrounds, Billings," Montana (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1095
    - Bull Elk with Cow Elk (Box 5, Folder 10)
      TP1096
    - Elk Running (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1097
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1098
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1099
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1100
    - Bull Elk (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1101
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1102
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1103
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1104
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1105
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1106
    - Elk Near Cliff Face (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1107
    - Elk Herd (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1108
    - Elk Herd (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1109
    - Elk Herd (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1110
    - Elk Herd (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1111
    - Elk Herd (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1112
    - Elk Herd (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1113
    - Elk Herd (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1114
    - Sheep Near Stream (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1115
    - Sheep Near Stream (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1116
    - Sheep with Sheep Wagon (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1117
    - Sheep (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1118
    - Sheep (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1119
    - Sheep (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1120
    - Sheep (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1121
    - Sheep (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1122
    - Lamb Nursing (Box 5, Folder 11)
      TP1123
    - Sheep With Sheep Wagon (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1124
    - Sheep with Sheep Wagon (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1125
    - Sheep on Hillside (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1126
    - Sheep - Postcard (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1127
    - Sheep Near Brush (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1128
    - Sheep (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1129
    - "Sheep on the Range" (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1130
    - Sheep (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1131
    - Sheep on Hillside (Box 5, Folder 12)
      TP1132
    - Sheep with Farm Buildings in Background (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1133
    - Bighorn Sheep (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1134
    - Bobcat Head - Mounted (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1135
    - Bobcat Head - Mounted (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1136
    - Bobcat Head - Mounted (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1137
    - Bobcat Head - Mounted - Print of Painting (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1138
    - Moose Head - Mounted (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1139
    - Buffalo Skull (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1140
    - Antelope (Box 5, Folder 13)
      TP1141
    - People in Tipi - Unidentified Painting (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1142
    - Three Native Americans - Unidentified Painting (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1143
    - J. Sharp Painting of Man in Tipi (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1144
    - "The Sentinel" (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1145
      Throssel ID #"©" 1920
      1 celluloid negative 6½ x 8½
    - Plenty Coups (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1146
      Throssel ID #"©" 1927
    - Waterfall (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1147
    - "The Ford Where the Bozeman Trail Crosses the Little Big Horn" (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1148
      Throssel ID #"©" 1922
    - "A Break in the Circle" (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1149
    - ("Coulson 1880" The First Town of Billings, Montana) (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1150
    - "In the Beartooth Mountains" (Box 5, Folder 14)
      TP1151
      Throssel ID #"©" 1923
    - "The Yellowstone Trail - Original Trail 1880" (Box 5, Folder 15)
      TP1152
    - Stagecoach - Holdup (Box 5, Folder 15)
      TP1153
    - "Rim Rocks Near Billings" Montana (Box 5, Folder 15)
      TP1154
      Throssel ID #"©" 1919
    - "Missed" (Box 5, Folder 16)
      TP1155
    - Hunting Buffalo (Box 5, Folder 16)
      TP1156
    - Moose (Box 5, Folder 16)
      TP1157
    - Antelope (Box 5, Folder 16)
      TP1158
    - "Battle of Royal Elk - An Eight Point Buck has a 'Royal Head'" (Box 5, Folder 16)
      TP1159
    - "Bugler of the High Ridges" (Box 5, Folder 16)
      TP1160
    - "Holdup Cut" - 15 Minutes West of Billings, Montana (Box 5, Folder 16)
      TP1161
    - "Caught" (Box 5, Folder 16)
      TP1162
      Throssel ID #"©" applied for
      nitrate negative
    - "The Land of the Indian" - Advertisement (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1163
      Negative Box 45
      1 lantern slide 3 x 4
    - "Indian Pictures - Special $1.00 this Week" - Advertisement (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1164
    - "Throssel Photographer" - Advertisement (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1165
    - Throssel Trademark (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1166
    - "Western Classics from the Land of the Indian" - Advertisement (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1167
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1168
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1169
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1170
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1171
    - Tipi near River (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1172
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1173
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1174
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1175
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1176
    - Catalog Page of Indian Prints (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1177
    - Old Faithful - Yellowstone Park, Wyoming (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1178
    - Old Faithful - Yellowstone Park, Wyoming (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1179
    - Upper Falls of the Yellowstone River - Yellowstone Park, Wyoming (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1180
    - River Geyser? - Yellowstone Park, Wyoming (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1181
    - Grotto Geyser - Yellowstone Park, Wyoming (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1182
    - Man Hunting in Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1183
    - Man Hunting in Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1184
    - Man Hunting Near Beartooth Butte (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1185
    - Man Hunting in the Beartooth Mountains (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1186
    - Fort C. F. Smith - Ruins (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1187
    - Reflection of Trees on River (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1188
    - Reflection of Trees on River (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1188A
    - Reflection of Trees on River (Box 5, Folder 17)
      TP1188B
    - Ridge Over Yellowstone(?) River (Box 5, Folder 18)
      TP1189
    - Yellowstone(?) River (Box 5, Folder 18)
      TP1190
    - Stream (Box 5, Folder 18)
      TP1191
    - Mountain River (Box 5, Folder 18)
      TP1192
    - Rock Creek Near Red Lodge, Montana(?) (Box 5, Folder 18)
      TP1193
    - Rock Creek Near Red Lodge, Montana(?) (Box 5, Folder 18)
      TP1194
    - Mountain Peak - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 18)
      TP1195
    - Mountain Peak - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 18)
      TP1196
    - Mountain Peak - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 19)
      TP1197
    - Mountain Peak - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 19)
      TP1198
    - Rock Creek(?) (Box 5, Folder 19)
      TP1199
    - Rock Creek(?) (Box 5, Folder 19)
      TP1200
    - Stream - Closeup (Box 5, Folder 19)
      TP1201
    - Mountain River (Box 5, Folder 19)
      TP1202
    - Rapids (Box 5, Folder 19)
      TP1203
    - Lake with Mountain Peak in Background (Box 5, Folder 20)
      TP1204
    - Rosebud Lake (Box 5, Folder 20)
      TP1205
    - Man Overlooking Mountain Lake (Box 5, Folder 20)
      TP1206
    - Beartooth Lake (Box 5, Folder 20)
      TP1207
    - Beartooth Lake with Beartooth Butte in Background (Box 5, Folder 20)
      TP1208
    - Cabin in Mountains (Box 5, Folder 20)
      TP1209
    - Mountain Covered in Trees (Box 5, Folder 20)
      TP1210
    - Mountain Peak with Dead Trees in Foreground (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1211
    - Mountain Side Covered with Snow (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1212
    - "Pine Lodge" Porch - View (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1213
    - Man with Horses at Mouth of Canyon (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1214
    - Four Men Climbing Rock Ledge (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1215
    - Two Men Near Rock Ledge (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1216
    - Rock Ledge (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1217
    - Car Near Rock Ledge (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1218
    - Two Men Near Rock Ledge (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1219
    - Rock Ledge - View (Box 5, Folder 21)
      TP1220
    - Rock Ledge (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1221
    - Rock Ledge (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1222
    - Hill with Rocky Ledges (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1223
    - Prairies with Hills in Background (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1224
    - Prairies with Hills in Background (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1225
    - Cottonwood Trees with Farm Buildings in Background (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1226
    - Cottonwood Trees with Farm Buildings in Background (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1227
    - Road by Rosebud Lake (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1228
    - Road Through Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1229
    - Two Old Trees on Hill Side (Box 5, Folder 22)
      TP1230
    - Wild Flowers (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1231
    - Trail Through Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1232
    - Mountain Silhouette (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1233
    - Horse Herd at Mountain Lake (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1234
    - River Overlook (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1235
    - River Running by Grove of Trees (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1236
    - River Running by Grove of Trees (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1237
    - River Running by Grove of Trees (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1238
    - River Running by Grove of Trees (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1239
      1 celluloid negative 2½ x 3
    - River Running by Mountain (Box 5, Folder 23)
      TP1240
    - River Running Through Canyon (Box 5, Folder 24)
      TP1241
    - Waterfall (Box 5, Folder 24)
      TP1242
    - River Running Through Valley (Box 5, Folder 24)
      TP1243
    - River Running Through Canyon (Box 5, Folder 24)
      TP1244
    - River Rapids - Close up (Box 5, Folder 24)
      TP1245
    - Horses in River - Side of a Mountain in Background (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1246
    - River with Trees in Foreground (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1247
    - Stream Running Through Grove of Trees (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1248
    - River with Mountain Side in Background (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1249
    - River Running by Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1250
    - River Running by Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1251
    - River Running by Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1252
    - River Running by Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1253
    - River Running by Tree Grove (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1254
    - Mountain with Trees and Vegetation in Foreground (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1255
    - Mountain Prairie with Car (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1256
    - Man Rowing Boat in Mountain Lake (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1257
    - Mountain Lakes - Possibly in Beartooth Mountains (Box 5, Folder 25)
      TP1258
    - Beartooth Lake with Bridge in Foreground (Box 5, Folder 26)
      TP1259
    - Mountain Valley (Box 5, Folder 26)
      TP1260
    - Road Through Mountain Valley (Box 5, Folder 26)
      TP1261
    - White Mountain in Sunlight Valley, Wyoming [?] (Box 5, Folder 26)
      TP1262
    - Mountain Being Covered by Clouds (Box 5, Folder 26)
      TP1263
    - Prairie with Mountain in Background (Box 5, Folder 27)
      TP1264
    - Mountain Silhouette (Box 5, Folder 27)
      TP1265
    - High Altitude Mountain - Possibly in Beartooth Mountains (Box 5, Folder 27)
      TP1266
      1 celluloid negative 2½ x 4½
    - Treeless Mountain (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1267
    - Mountain Silhouette (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1268
    - Mountain Silhouette (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1269
    - Tree Covered Ridge (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1270
    - Mountain - Unidentified - Field in Foreground (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1271
      1 celluloid negative 2½ x 5½
    - Mountain Valley with Building (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1272
    - People on Cliff (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1273
    - Rock Formation - Unusual (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1274
    - Valley with Cliffs Off the Side - Car Hood in Foreground (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1275
    - Rock Formation - Unusual (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1276
    - Rock Formation (Unusual) with Two Women (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1277
    - Rock Formation - Unusual (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1278
    - Rock Outcrop (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1279
    - River Running Through Canyon (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1280
    - Rock Cliffs (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1281
    - Rock Cliffs (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1282
    - Rock Cliffs (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1283
    - Prairie with Cloudy Sky (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1284
    - Rock Pile - Unusual (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1285
    - Cloudy Sky with Telephone Pole in Foreground (Box 6, Folder 1)
      TP1286
    - Cloudscape (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1287
    - Cloudscape (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1288
    - Cloudscape (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1289
    - Landscape Through Barbed Wire Fence (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1290
      1 celluloid negative 2½ x 3½
    - Prairie with Mountain in Background (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1291
    - Prairie Landscape (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1292
    - Prairie with Mountain in Background (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1293
    - Prairie with Mountain in Background (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1294
    - Mountain Prairie Covered with Snow (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1295
    - Frozen Mountain Lake (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1296
    - Pine Trees Covered with Snow (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1297
    - Road Near Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1298
    - Brush Growing Near Stream (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1299
    - Brush Growing Near Stream (Box 6, Folder 2)
      TP1300
    - Brush - Close-up (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1301
    - Brush - Closeup (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1302
    - Yucca Plant (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1303
    - Hill Covered with Vegetation (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1304
    - Tree Grove Near Road (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1305
    - Fence Near Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1306
    - Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1307
    - Man Near River and a Tree (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1308
    - Pine Trees (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1309
    - Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 3)
      TP1310
      1 celluloid negative 2 x 3
    - Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1311
    - Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1312
    - Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1313
    - Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1314
    - Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1315
    - Tree with Lone Horseback Rider (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1316
    - Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1317
    - Cactus (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1318
    - Cactus (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1319
    - Road by Tree Grove (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1320
    - Billings, Montana(?) in Winter (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1321
    - Montana(?) in Winter (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1322
    - Billings Fairgrounds(?) (Box 6, Folder 4)
      TP1323
    - Grave Near Base of Pine Tree [?] (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1324
    - Grave Near Base Of Pine Tree [?] (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1325
    - Bridge Over Small Stream (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1326
    - Bridge Over Small Stream (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1327
    - Bridge Over Small Stream (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1328
    - River Scenes (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1329
    - Railroad Tracks Near River (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1330
    - Railroad Tracks in Prairie (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1331
    - Railroad Tracks in Prairie (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1332
    - Mount Baker(?), Washington - Postcard (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1333
    - Mount Baker(?), Washington - Postcard (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1334
    - Mount Rainier - Postcard (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1335
    - Multiplex Falls Black Hills, South Dakota - Postcard (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1336
    - "Castle Rock" Badlands, South Dakota - Postcard (Box 6, Folder 5)
      TP1337
    - Cloudscape (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1338
    - Cloudscape Over Prairie (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1339
    - Cloudscape Over Prairie (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1340
    - Cloudscape Over Prairie (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1341
    - Cloudscape Over Prairie (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1342
    - Telephone Poles Waiting to be Set (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1343
    - Telephone Pole without Wires (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1344
    - Telephone Pole with Wires (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1345
      AHC Neg. #25163
    - Telephone Pole with Wires (Box 6, Folder 6)
      TP1346
      AHC Neg. #25164
    - Trees Reflecting Image Off River (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1347
      AHC Neg. #25165
    - River Bend (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1348
      AHC Neg. #25166
    - River Ford (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1349
      AHC Neg. #25167
    - Riverbank Covered with Brush and Trees (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1350
    - River with Deep Foliage on Both Sides (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1351
    - Riverbank - Man and Horses on Bank (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1352
    - Trees and Fence Reflecting Image on River (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1353
    - Little Big Horn River (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1354
    - River Bend (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1355
    - River (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1356
    - Stream Surrounded by Foliage - Man on Horse Leading Two Horses (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1357
    - Riverbank with Trees (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1358
    - River Bend (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1359
    - Fast Running River (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1360
    - Fast Running River (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1361
    - Snow Covered Trees on River Bank (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1362
      AHC Neg. #25168
    - Riverbank Covered with Snow (Box 6, Folder 7)
      TP1363
      AHC Neg. #25169
    - River Bend in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1364
    - River Bend in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1365
    - River Bend in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1366
    - River Bend in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1367
    - River Bend in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1368
    - River Bend in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1369
    - River Bend in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1370
    - Trees and Brush Covered with Snow (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1371
      AHC Neg. #25170
    - Road Through Snow Covered Trees (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1372
      AHC Neg. #25171
    - Riverbank Covered in Snow (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1373
    - Ravine Covered in Snow (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1374
    - River Bend in Winter (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1375
    - Snow Drift (Box 6, Folder 8)
      TP1376